invenglobal.com 2019-12-24

# InvenGlobal - The Esports Company

##### **Introduction**

Inven Global English, LLC.("Invenglobal") and any and all of its affiliates ("Company" or "We") respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this privacy policy (this "policy").

This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit the website Invenglobal (our "Website") and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting and disclosing that information.

This policy is subject to and in addition to our Terms of Service.

This policy applies to all information we collect:

  * On this Website.
  * In e-mail, text and other electronic messages between you and this Website.
  * When you interact with our advertising and applications on third-party websites and services, if those applications or advertising include links to this policy.
  * In other ways that we describe to you at the point of collection or otherwise with your consent.

It does not apply to information collected by:

  * us offline or through any other means, including on any other website operated by Company or any third party (including our affiliates and subsidiaries); or
  * any third party (including our affiliates and subsidiaries), including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from or on the Website

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Website. By accessing or using this Website, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time (see Changes to our Privacy Policy below). Your continued use of this Website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.

##### **Children Under the Age of 13**

Our Website is not intended for children under 13 years of age. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to or on the Website. We do NOT knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you are under 13, do not provide any information on this Website or on or through any of its features/register on the Website, make any purchases through the Website, use any of the interactive or public comment features of this Website or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address or any screen name or user name you may use. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [desk@invenglobal.com](mailto:desk@invenglobal.com).

##### **Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It**

We collect several types of information from and about users of our Website, including information:

  * Directly from you when you provide it to us.  
 
    * The information you must provide when you sign up for an account:  
Username, Country, Email Address
    * This information can be checked on your Account Page after logging in, and you can update or fix your information yourself. 
    * Invenglobal verifies your email address for identification.
    * Your personal contact information will not be passed to any other organization. It will only be used for you to log in to our Website.
    * This information will be safely stored in a secure system within the U.S.
    * If you request that we shut down your account or delete your information, we will disable your account within a reasonable period of time and delete your information accordingly.
  * Automatically as you navigate through the Website. Information collected automatically may include without limitation usage details, IP addresses and information collected through cookies, web beacons and other tracking technologies.

Information You Provide to Us

The information we collect on or through our Website may include:

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Website. This includes information provided at the time of registering to use certain features of our Website or posting material. We may also ask you for information when you enter a contest or promotion sponsored by us, and when you report a problem with our Website.
  * Records and copies of your correspondence (including e-mail addresses), if you contact us.  
Your responses to polls, surveys or questions that we might ask you to complete.
  * Your search queries on the Website.

You also may provide information to be published or displayed (hereinafter, "posted") on public areas of the Website, or transmitted to other users of the Website or third parties (collectively, "User Contributions"). Your User Contributions are posted on and transmitted to others at your own risk. Although we limit access to certain pages, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. Additionally, we cannot control the actions of other users of the Website with whom you may choose to share your User Contributions. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that your User Contributions will not be viewed by unauthorized persons.

Information We Collect Through Automatic Data Collection Technologies.

As you navigate through and interact with our Website, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions and patterns:

  * Details of your visits to our Website, including traffic data, location data, logs and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Website.
  * Information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system and browser type.

The information we collect automatically is statistical data. It helps us to improve our Website and to deliver a better and more personalized service, including by enabling us to:

  * Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.
  * Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Website according to your individual interests.
  * Speed up your searches.
  * Recognize you when you return to our Website.

We use cookies and similar technology (e.g. web beacons, pixels, and ad tags) to show you relevant advertising on our site. We also use cookies to learn how users visit our site. Our partners may also use cookies to determine whether we’ve shown an ad and how it performed. You can opt out of the cookies from the link below.

The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:

  * Cookies (or browser cookies). A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website.
  * Flash Cookies. Certain features of our Website may use local stored objects (or Flash cookies) to collect and store information about your preferences and navigation to, from and on our Website. Flash cookies are not managed by the same browser settings as are used for browser cookies. For information about managing your privacy and security settings for Flash cookies, see Choices about How We Use and Disclose Your Information below.
  * Any industry standard data and website information collection methodologies then in existence

How do we save your cookies:

  * Our Website does not save your personal data when we use your cookies. You can easily erase cookies from your computer or mobile device using your browser. For instructions on how to handle and delete cookies please look under "Help" in your browser. You can choose to disable cookies, or to receive a notification each time a new cookie is sent to your computer or mobile device. Please note that if you choose to disable cookies, you will not be able to take advantage of all our features.

##### **How We Use Your Information**

We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information:

  * To present our Website and its contents to you.
  * To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us.
  * To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it.
  * To notify you about changes to our Website or any products or services we offer or provide through it.
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features on our Website.
  * In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.
  * For any purposes permitted under this policy or the Terms of Service.
  * For any other purpose with your consent.

We may use the information we have collected from you to enable us to display advertisements to our advertisers' target audiences. Even though we do not disclose your personal information for these purposes without your consent, if you click on or otherwise interact with an advertisement, the advertiser may assume that you meet its target criteria.

##### **Disclosure of Your Information**

We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction.

We may disclose the information that we collect or you provide as described in this privacy policy:

  * To contractors, service providers and other third parties we use to support our business and who are bound by contractual obligations to keep the information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them.
  * To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other sale or transfer of some or all of the Company's assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by the Company about our Website users is among the assets transferred.
  * To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it.
  * For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.  
With your consent.

We may also disclose your personal information:

  * To comply with any court order, law or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.
  * To enforce or apply our Terms of Service and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes.
  * If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of the Company, other users of the Website, our customers or others.

##### **Accessing and Correcting Your Information**

You can review and change your personal information by logging into the Website and visiting your account profile page.

If you delete your User Contributions from the Website, copies of your User Contributions may remain viewable in cached and archived pages, or might have been copied or stored by other Website users. Proper access and use of information provided on the Website, including User Contributions, is governed by our Terms of Service.

##### **Your California Privacy Rights**

California "Shine the Light" law permits users of our Website that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to [desk@invenglobal.com](mailto:desk@invenglobal.com).

##### **Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to modify, amend, alter or change this policy at any time for any reason or no reason. It is our policy to post any changes we make to our privacy policy on this page. If we make material changes to how we treat our users' personal information, we will notify you through a notice on the Website home page. The date the privacy policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date active and deliverable e-mail address for you, and for periodically visiting our Website and this privacy policy to check for any changes.

##### **Contact Information**

To ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and our privacy practices, contact us at:

Email: [desk@invenglobal.com](mailto:desk@invenglobal.com)

##### **Further Information and Contact Details**

We have appointed a Data Protection Officer to ensure that we continuously process your personal data in an open, accurate, and legal manner. You can contact our Data Protection Officer at desk@invenglobal.com and write a DPO.

By email: [desk@invenglobal.com](mailto:desk@invenglobal.com)

By telephone: +1-949-576-2867
